###### Featured

Media is more complex than ever. Discover the future of cross-media measurement with Nielsen ONE.

#### **Type**

#### **Topic**

###### Featured

Explore what consumers are watching, playing and listening to around the world.

en

Solutions

Insights

Data Center

About

Search

en

### Additional privacy information

#### For Nielsen

##### [Our Privacy Principles](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/privacy-principles/)

##### [Careers Privacy Notice](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/privacy-principles/careers-privacy-statement/)

##### [](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/privacy-principles/marketing-privacy-statement/)[](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/privacy-principles/marketing-privacy-statement/)[Digital Measurement Privacy Notice](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/privacy-principles/digital-measurement-privacy-statement/)

##### [Marketing Privacy Notice](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/privacy-principles/marketing-privacy-statement/)

##### [Marketing Cloud Privacy Notice](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/privacy-principles/nielsen-marketing-cloud-services-privacy-statement/)

##### [Website Privacy Notice](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/privacy-principles/website-privacy-statement/)

##### Client Communications Privacy Notice

#### For Gracenote

##### [Gracenote Privacy Notice](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/gracenote-privacy-statement/)

##### [Gracenote Services Privacy Notice](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/gracenote-services-privacy-statement/)

##### [Gracenote Sports Privacy Notice](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/gracenote-sports-privacy-statement/)

##### [Gracenote Terms of Use](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/gracenote-terms-of-use/)

##### [Gracenote Open Source Software](https://www.nielsen.com/legal/gracenote-open-source-notice/)

#### Need more help?

Privacy questions can be submitted by email to: [privacy.department@nielsen.com](mailto:privacy.department@nielsen.com?Subject=Nielsen%20Privacy%20Questions)

Stay in the loop
----------------

Keep up-to-date with our weekly newsletter, Media Pulse.

Notice: JavaScript is required for this content.

* * *

Copyright © 2024 The Nielsen Company (US), LLC. All Rights Reserved.

[粤ICP备17078252号](https://beian.miit.gov.cn/) | [粤公网安备44010402001179号](https://beian.miit.gov.cn/) | 上海尼尔森市场研究有限公司广州分公司

Contact us

### Find the right solution for your business

In an ever-changing world, we’re here to help you stay ahead of what’s to come with the tools to measure, connect with, and engage your audiences.

##### How can we help?

Notice: JavaScript is required for this content.
